Finding Aid for American Society for Information Science and Technology Records, 1925-2001
University of Michigan Library (Special Collections Research Center)
- RELATED ORGANIZATIONS AND SUBJECTS
  - Council of Communication Societies (CCS), 1970-1972 and 1977 (Box 161)
  - Council of Library Association Executives (CLAE), 1979 (Box 161)
  - Council on Library Resources (CLR)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 161)
    - Miscellanea, 1976-1977 (Box 161)
    - Newsletters: "Recent Developments," 1972-1982 (Box 161)
  - Council of Professional Associations on Federal Statistics, 1982 (Box 161)
  - Council on Documentation Research, 1958-1960 (Box 161)
  - Council on Library Associations
    - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 161)
    - Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 161)
    - News Releases and Brochures, 1978-1981 (Box 161)
  - Crawford Information Systems, 1977 (Box 161)
  - Curriculum Development, 1972 (Box 161)
  - DEVSIS Newsletter, 1975 (Box 161)
  - Data Processing Management Association (DPMA), 1977-1978 1987 (Box 161)
  - Dataflow Systems, 1976-1979 (Box 161)
  - Definitions of Information Science, 1970 and 1973 (Box 161)
  - Directories
    - Articles About, 1969-1977 (Box 161)
    - Correspondence, 1971 and 1979-1981 (Box 161)
  - Documentation Abstracts
    - Board Correspondence, 1964-1969, 3 folders (Box 161)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1979, 3 folders (Box 161)
      (includes correspondence with SLA, ACS, Aslib, et al.)
    - Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 161)
    - Minutes, 1966-1969, 2 folders (Box 161)
  - Documentation Society, undated (Box 162)
  - Domestic Council Committee on the Right of Privacy, 1976 (Box 162)
  - Drug Information Association, 1975 (Box 162)
  - Educational Media Yearbook, 1975-1976 (Box 162)
  - Educational Resources Information Center (ERIC)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 162)
    - Miscellanea, 1976-1977 (Box 162)
    - Publications, 1978 (Box 162)
    - Quarterly Progress Reports, 1977 (Box 162)
  - Electronic Mail Association, 1985 (Box 162)
  - ERIC Clearinghouse on Library and Information Sciences
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1973, 2 folders (Box 162)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1970 and undated (Box 162)
    - Proposals to the National Science Foundation
      - September 1, 1969 (Box 162)
      - September 10, 1969 (Box 162)
      - October 1, 1969 (Box 162)
    - Proposals to the U.S. Office of Education
      - September 1, 1969 (Box 162)
      - October 1, 1969 (Box 162)
      - October 14, 1969 (Box 162)
  - Encyclopedia of Library and Information Science, undated (Box 162)
  - Engineering Information, Inc., 1982 (Box 162)
  - European Association of Information Services (EUSIDIC), 1986 (Box 162)
  - The European On-Line Information Network (EURONET), 1976 (Box 162)
  - FASEB Placement Service, 1965 (Box 162)
  - F. W. Faxon Company, 1978 (Box 162)
  - Federal DP Expo, 1981 (Box 162)
  - Federal Information Research Science and Technology Network, 1969 (Box 162)
  - Federal Library and Information Committee (FLICC), 1988 (Box 162)
  - Federal Library Committee (FLC)
    - Agenda and Summary, 1971-1973 and 1980 (Box 162)
    - Annual Reports, 1974 (Box 162)
    - Executive Secretary's Comments, 1972 (Box 162)
    - Miscellanea, 1972 and 1979 (Box 162)
    - Study of Federal Library/Information Service Staffing, 1978 (Box 162)
  - Federal Professional Association, 1980-1981 (Box 162)
  - Foundation Center, 1976 and 1979 (Box 162)
  - German Foundation for International Development, 1975 (Box 162)
  - IDCAS, undated (Box 162)
  - ISTDB (Information Science and Technology Data Base), undated (Box 162)
  - Illinois State Library Advisory Committee on Education and Training, 1971-1975 (Box 162)
  - Inform Seminars, 1980 (Box 162)
  - Information and Publishing Systems, 1978 (Box 162)
  - The Information Bank, 1976-1979 (Box 162)
  - Information Clearinghouse, 1975 (Box 162)
  - Information Engineering, 1974-1975 (Box 162)
  - Information Industry Association (IIA)
    - Bulletin, 1970 (Box 162)
    - Conferences, 1970-1976 (Box 162)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1980 (Box 162)
    - Information Action, 1971 (Box 162)
    - Membership Lists, 1970 (Box 162)
    - Minutes, 1970 (Box 162)
    - Miscellanea, 1971-1972 (Box 162)
    - News Releases, 1974-1980 1988 (Box 162)
    - Progress Report, 1983 (Box 162)
  - Information Manager, 1979 (Box 162)
  - Information Resources Administration Councils (IRAC), 1983-1986 (Box 162)
  - Information Retrieval and Library Automation, 1979 (Box 162)
  - Information Science Abstracts (ISA), 1975-1978 and 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box 162)
  - Information Science and Technology Association, Japan (INFOSTA), 1988 (Box 162)
  - Information Science Corporation, 1979-1980 (Box 162)
  - Information Specialists, 1979 (Box 162)
  - Information Technology Associates, 1979 (Box 162)
  - Information Utilities Conference, 1981 (Box 162)
  - Infoscope, 1981 (Box 162)
  - Infoterm, 1985 (Box 162)
  - Institute for Information Policy and Research, 1980 (Box 162)
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE),1984-1985 1988 and undated (Box 162)
  - Institute of Information Scientists (IIS), 1971-1981 1983-1984 (Box 162)
  - Intergovernmental Bureau for Informatics (IBI), 1981 (Box 162)
  - International Center for Information Technologies (ICIT), 1988 (Box 162)
  - International Conference on Computer Communications, 1972-1973 (Box 162)
  - International Cultural and Trade Center Foundation, 1974 (Box 162)
  - International Federation for Documentation (FID)
    - Budget, 1975 (Box 162)
    - Committees
      - Committee on Linguistics in Documentation, 1975-1980 (Box 162)
      - Documentation Terminology Committee, 1976 (Box 163)
      - Education and Training Committee, 1971-1973 and 1980 (Box 163)
      - Executive Committee, 1976 (Box 163)
      - Program Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 163)
      - United States National Committee
        - Correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box 163)
        - Minutes, 1975 (Box 163)
        - Nominations, 1976 (Box 163)
        - Program Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 163)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1976 1980-1983 1986 1988, 5 folders (Box 163)
      (year 1975 re publication distribution)
    - Council
      - Agenda, 1975 (Box 163)
      - Reports, 1975 (Box 163)
    - Dues Structure, 1976 (Box 163)
    - Financial Information, 1974-1975 (Box 163)
    - Miscellanea, 1975-1981 (Box 163)
    - Reports, 1972 and undated (Box 163)
    - Statutes, 1983 (Box 163)
    - Symposia and Conferences
      - 33rd Conference of FID and International Congress on Documentation, Tokyo, 1967
        - List of Participants (Box 163)
      - The Hague, 1974 (Box 163)
      - Brussels, 1975
        - Memos (Box 163)
        - Papers (Box 163)
        - Program and List of Participants (Box 163)
        - Reports (Box 163)
      - Finland, 1985 (Box 163)
      - Mexico City, 1976
        - Agenda and Program (Box 163)
        - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 163)
        - News Releases (Box 163)
        - Regulations (Box 163)
      - Edinburgh, 1978 (Box 163)
      - Copenhagen, 1980 (Box 163)
      - Hong Kong, 1982 (Box 163)
  - International Federation for Information Processing (IFIP), 1977-1980 1983-1986 (Box 163)
  - International Federation of Library Associations (IFLA), 1981 1985 1989 (Box 163)
  - International Office of Bibliography, undated (Box 163)
  - International Organization for Standardization (ISO), 1975 (Box 163)
  - Joint Agreements Group (JAG), 1969 (Box 163)
  - Joint Venture, 1975 (Box 163)
  - King Research, Inc.
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 164)
    - Paper: "Concepts for Evaluating Information Centers" with attachments, 16 folders (Box 164)
  - Knowledge Industry Publications, INC. (KIPI), 1978-1980 (Box 164)
  - Latham Press Corporation, 1976 (Box 164)
  - Legislation
    - Bills, 1969 (Box 164)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 164)
  - Librarian of Congress: Opposition to Appointment of Daniel Boorstin, 1975 (Box 164)
  - The Library Automation Research and Consulting Association, 1971-1973 (Box 164)
  - Library Education, 1970-1972 and 1979 (Box 164)
  - Library Journal, 1978 (Box 164)
  - Library of Congress Network Advisory Committee, 1978 (Box 165)
  - Library Partnership Act, 1975 (Box 165)
  - Marc Update Service, 1975-1977 (Box 165)
  - Medical Library Association (MLA), 1946 1975 1984 1988 1989 and undated (Box 165)
  - Microcard Editions, 1975-1976 (Box 165)
  - Miscellanea, 1976-1981 (Box 165)
  - National Academy of Science, 1976 (Box 165)
  - National Advisory Commission on Libraries, 1967 (Box 165)
  - National Association for State Information Systems (NASIS), 1975 (Box 165)
  - National Association of Government Archives and Records Administration (NAGARA), 1983-1987 (Box 165)
  - National Association of State Information Resource Executives (NASIR), 1990-1991 (Box 165)
  - National Audio Visual Association (NAVA), 1972-1973 (Box 165)
  - National Auxiliary Publications Service (NAPS)
    - Agreement between ASIS and Microfiche Systems Corporation, 1972 (Box 165)
    - Agreement between ASIS and Research and Microfilm Publications, undated (Box 165)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1973, 4 folders (Box 165)
  - National Bureau of Standards, 1964 regarding the Symposium on Statistical Association Methods for Mechanized Documentation (Box 165)
  - The National Center for Law Information
    - Miscellanea, 1971-1974 (Box 165)
    - Proposal: "National Center for Law Information Concept: A Discussion," 1970 (Box 165)
  - National Citizens Committee for Broadcasting, 1979 (Box 165)
  - National Commission on Libraries and Information Science (NCLIS)
    - Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 165)
    - Correspondence
      - 1971-1976, 3 folders (Box 165)
      - 1977-1988, 3 folders (Box 166)
    - Meeting Agenda, 1979-1980 (Box 166)
    - Membership List, 1973 (Box 166)
    - Miscellanea, 1970-1975 (Box 166)
    - News Releases, 1971-1982, 5 folders (Box 166)
    - Paperwork Reduction Act, 1989-1990 (Box 166)
    - Proposal: regarding the National Program for Libraries and Information Science, 1973 (Box 166)
    - Report Drafts, 1974 (Box 166)
    - Reprints and Photocopies, 1974 and 1978 (Box 166)
    - Study: "Elements of Information Resources Policy..." by Anthony G. Oettinger, 1975 (Box 166)
    - Task Force on American National Standards Institute Committee, 1977 (Box 166)
      (includes Activities and Future Directions)
    - Testimony
      - Before Subcommittee on Education of the Senate Labor and Public Welfare Committee, 1969 (Box 166)
      - Before NCLIS, 1974 (Box 166)
  - National Computer Conference (NCC), 1975-1976 1985-1986, 2 folders (Box 166)
  - National Council on Quality Continuing Education, Information, Library, Media Personnel, 1980 (Box 166)
  - National Federation of Abstracting and Indexing Services (NFAIS)
    - ANSI Z-39 and Standards, 1977-1981 (Box 166)
    - Annual Report, 1974 and 1980 (Box 166)
    - Assembly Business Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 166)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 1977-1980 (Box 166)
    - Brochures, including History of Organizations, scattered dates (Box 166)
    - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 166)
    - Bylaws, 1978 (Box 166)
    - Conferences, 1975-1980 1985 (Box 166)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1987, 8 folders (Box 166)
    - Financial Information, 1980 (Box 166)
    - Government and International Relations Committee, 1979 (Box 166)
    - Marketing Committee, 1975-1979 includes Minutes (Box 166)
    - Member Service Supplement, 1974-1981 (Box 166)
    - Membership, 1973-1981 includes 1978 Directory (Box 166)
    - Miscellanea, 1978 (Box 166)
    - News Releases, 1974-1981 (Box 166)
    - Newsletters, 1977-1979 (Box 166)
    - Officers, 1973-1974 (Box 166)
    - Reports, 1974 (Box 166)
  - National Indian Omnibus Library Bill, undated (Box 166)
  - National Information Retrieval Colloquium (NIRC), 1976 (Box 167)
  - National Information Standards Organization (NISO), 1981-1989 (Box 167)
  - National Labor Association Processing Company, 1975-1977 (Box 167)
  - National Library of Medicine, 1971-1972 and 1975 (Box 167)
  - National Micrographics Association
    - Association Interface Committee, 1980 (Box 167)
    - Miscellanea, 1974-1981 (Box 167)
      (includes membership directory)
  - National Online Circuit, 1980 (Box 167)
  - National Periodicals Center, 1979-1981 (Box 167)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF)
    - Congressional Committee Membership, 1976 (Box 167)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1980, 10 folders (Box 167)
    - Information Science and Technology, 1974-1978 (Box 167)
    - Miscellanea, scattered dates (Box 167)
    - Office of Science Information Services, 1973-1974 (Box 167)
    - Organizational Directory and Chart, 1974 and 1980 (Box 167)
    - Program Announcements, 1977-1979 (Box 167)
    - Projects, 1963 and 1975 (Box 167)
    - Proposals, 1978-1979 (Box 167)
    - Science Information Activities Task Force
      - Charter, 1976 (Box 167)
      - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 167)
      - History, 1977 (Box 167)
        (includes miscellanea)
      - Membership, 1977 (Box 167)
      - Minutes, 1977 (Box 167)
    - Statements: before Congressional Committees, 1974-1975 and 1978 (Box 167)
  - National Technical Information Service (Department of Commerce), 1973-1977 (Box 167)
  - National Telecommunications and Information Administration (Department of Commerce), 1978-1979 (Box 167)
  - National Translation Center, 1975 (Box 167)
  - New Worlds Video, 1976 (Box 167)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), 1966 and 1975-1976 (Box 167)
  - Online Review, 1980-1981 (Box 168)
  - On-Line Systems, 1979-1980 (Box 168)
  - On-Line Users, 1976 (Box 168)
  - Orb Foundation, 1975 (Box 168)
  - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD), 1974 and 1978 (Box 168)
  - Oriental Science Literature Service, ADI, 1941 (Box 168)
  - Pennsylvania Library Association, 1987 (Box 168)
  - People's Republic of China, 1987 (Box 168)
  - Pittsburgh, University of, undated (Box 168)
  - Placement Services, 1962-1968 and 1979 (Box 168)
  - Policy Studies Organization, 1979 (Box 168)
  - President's Committee on Science and Technology, 1977 (Box 168)
  - PRC Computer Center, 1975 (Box 168)
  - President's Forum, 1980-1982, 2 folders (Box 168)
  - Privacy Protection Study Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 168)
  - Program for Information Managers, 1978 (Box 168)
  - Program on Information Technologies and Public Policy, 1975-1976 (Box 168)
  - Public Relations, 1979-1980 (Box 168)
  - Reprint Requests, 1975-1979 (Box 168)
  - The Research Libraries Group, 1978-1980 (Box 168)
  - The Ringgold Corporation, 1975-1976 (Box 168)
  - Saracevic, Tefko, 1975 (Box 168)
  - Science Associates International, 1971 and 1975-1976 (Box 168)
  - Science Information Council (NSF, Office of Science Information Service)
    - Agendas, 1959-1974 (Box 168)
    - Contents, 1959-1971 (Box 168)
    - Meetings, 1959-1963, 3 folders (Box 168)
  - Science Service, 1925-1952 (Box 168)
    (organization headed by Watson Davis; predecessor to ADI)
  - Scientific Research Society, 1988 (Box 168)
  - Simulation Councils, Inc., 1967 (Box 168)
  - Smithsonian Science Information Exchange (SSIE), 1974 (Box 168)
  - Society for Scholarly Publishing, 1978-19791987 (Box 168)
  - Society for Technical Communication, 1974-1978 (Box 168)
  - Society of National Association Publications (SNAP), 1976 (Box 168)
  - Spartan Books, 1964-1967 (Box 168)
  - Special Libraries Association
    - Annual Meetings, 1971-1980, 6 folders (Box 169)
    - Articles and Tear Sheets, 1970-1980 (Box 169)
    - Brochures, 1979 and undated (Box 169)
    - Correspondence, 1947 1970-1988, 3 folders (Box 169)
    - Financial Information, 1975 (Box 169)
    - News Releases, 1976-1980 (Box 169)
  - State of New Jersey: Governor's Commission on Science and Technology, 1985 (Box 169)
  - UNESCO (United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization)
    - Editors of Documentation, 1972 (Box 169)
    - General Information Program (PGI)
      - Agenda and Program, 1978-1979 (Box 169)
      - Correspondence, 1948-19491975 1978-1979 1982-1984, 2 folders (Box 169)
      - Papers, 1968 1977-1979 (Box 169)
    - Information and Documentation Systems, Meeting on, 1975 (Box 169)
  - UNISIST, 1971 (Box 169)
  - UNISIT, 1978-1980 (Box 169)
  - USNCFID, 1959-1960 1976 (Box 169)
    (includes Correspondence)
  - U. S. Asiatic Company, 1976 (Box 169)
  - United States
    - Civil Service Commission
      - Correspondence
        - Civil Service Qualification Standards, GS 1410 and 1411 1971-1982 (Box 169)
        - Civil Service Qualification Standards, GS 1412 1973-1976 (Box 169)
        - Standards of U. S. Civil Service Commission, 1971 (Box 169)
    - Congress
      - House Resolution 4461 1975-1980 (Box 169)
      - House Subcommittee on Science, Research and Technology, 1974 (Box 169)
      - Office of Technology Assessment, 1989 (Box 169)
      - Subcommittee on Patent and Information Policy, 1978 (Box 169)
    - Department of
      - Agriculture, 1981 Reports from the Office of the Secretary (Box 169)
      - Commerce
        - National Technical Information Service (NTIS), 2000 (Box 169)
      - Education
        - Correspondence and News Releases, 1981 (Box 169)
        - Project Reports: "A Library and Information Science Research Agenda for the 1980s" 1981 (Box 169)
        - Projects, 1982 (Box 169)
    - Education, Office of: Summary Synthesis, 1976 (Box 169)
    - Management and Budget, Office of, 1980 (Box 169)
      (regarding Information System Policy)
    - National Commission for UNESCO, 1981 (Box 169)
    - Personnel Management, Office of, 1982 (Box 169)
  - Universities, 1972-1973 (Box 169)
  - University Microfilms, 1963-1970 (Box 169)
  - University of California: Institute of Library Research, 1973 (Box 169)
  - University of Chicago: Graduate Library School, 1968 (Box 169)
  - Urban Information Interpreters, 1973 (Box 169)
  - Urban Regional Information Systems Association (URISA), 1971-1973 (Box 169)
  - Videotapes, 1971-1972 (Box 169)
  - Welding and Testing Technology Exhibition and Conference (WATTec), 1987 (Box 169)
  - White House, 1974-1975 (Box 170)
  - White House Conference on Library and Information Services (WHCLIS)
    - Agenda, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Clippings File, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Company Brochures, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Conference Brochures, 1979-1980 (Box 170)
    - Conference Dates, 1978 (Box 170)
    - Congressional Resolutions, 1970-1974 (Box 170)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1978-1981 and undated, 8 folders (Box 170)
    - Delegates and Alternates, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Discussion Guides, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Films on Library and Information Sciences, 1979 Catalog (Box 170)
    - Glossary of Library and Information Science Terms, undated (Box 170)
    - Group Summary, 1979 (Box 170)
    - History, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Invitees and Attendees, May 1979-February 1980 and undated, 4 folders (Box 170)
    - Issue Papers, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Issues and Resolutions, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Miscellanea, 1979 (Box 170)
    - News Releases, 1977-1980, 2 folders (Box 170)
    - On-Line Databases, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Planning Program, July 1979 (Box 170)
    - Policy, undated (Box 170)
    - Pre-White House Conference, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Program, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Proposals and Statements
      - ASIS, 1978-1980 (Box 170)
      - Miscellaneous Organizations, 1973-1974 and 1978-1980 (Box 170)
      - National Commission on Libraries and Information Science, 1974 and 1978-1979 (Box 170)
      - Special Libraries Association, 1974 (Box 170)
    - Reference Book Collection, 1979 (Box 170)
    - Resolutions, 1979-1980 (Box 170)
    - State and Territorial Conferences, 4 folders (Box 171)
    - Summary and Final Report, undated (Box 171)
    - Theme Conference Summary, 1978-1979 (Box 171)
    - WHC Update, 1979 (Box 171)
    - World Congress of Universal Documentation, 1937 (Box 171)
  - White House Conference on Library and Information Services II
    - General, 19891990 (Box 171)
  - Zator Company: Calvin Mooers, 1950-1962 (Box 171)
- SPECIAL LIBRARIES ASSOCIATION MERGER
  The SPECIAL LIBRARIES ASSOCIATION MERGER series (1 linear foot) documents the process ASIS and SLA went through when they considered merging their organizations. The merger was not completed.
  - Annual Reports: of SLA Special Representative to ASIS, 1972-1974 (Box 172)
  - Articles regarding 1970-1971 (Box 172)
  - Chronology ASIS/SLA Merger Discussions, 1968-1970 (Box 172)
  - Comparison of ASIS and SLA, 1969-1970 (Box 172)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1975, 10 folders (Box 172)
  - Feasibility Study, 1969-1970 (Box 172)
  - Financial Information, 1968-1971, 3 folders (Box 172)
  - Implementation Plan, 1969-1970 (Box 172)
  - Joint Operating Group
    - Correspondence, 1963-1966, 2 folders (Box 172)
    - Reports, 1963-1966 (Box 172)
    - General, 1921-1957 1963-1971 and undated, 3 folders (Box 172)
      (years 1921-1957 primarly photocopies)
  - Membership, undated (Box 172)
  - Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 172)
  - Miscellanea, 1969-1970 (Box 172)
  - Motions, 1969-1970 (Box 172)
  - Paper: "ERIC/CLIS: An Information Resource for Librarians," 1970 (Box 172)
  - Proposal Advantages, 1969 (Box 172)
  - Questionnaire, 1970-1971 (Box 172)
  - Reel-to-Reel tapes, undated (Box 172)
  - Reports, 1970 (Box 172)
  - Special Libraries Association
    - Brochures, 1969-1970 and undated (Box 172)
    - Division Manual, 1970 (Box 172)
  - Tear Sheets and Photocopies, 1969-1971, 2 folders (Box 172)
- CONVENTION AUDIO/VIDEO TAPES
  The CONVENTION AUDIO/VIDEO TAPES series comprises sixteen linear feet, the bulk of which includes tapes of papers presented at the annual meetings, in addition to annual business meetings, plenary sessions, doctoral forums, special forums, special panels, and symposia. The tapes are arranged chronologically by convention starting in 1972. Most of the cassette boxes are labeled with a list of the titles and numbers assigned to all the tapes which were created. The library does not hold a complete set of tapes, however. Though there are some missing tapes for every convention, the convention tapes in this collection provide good documentation of the topics discussed at the annual meetings.
  There are a few scattered videotapes for the 1975, 1977, and 1980 conventions. Most of them are videocassettes in unidentified non-VHS formats. There are also two open reel (reel-to-reel) videotapes.
  A small amount of additional visual materials, including microfiche and photographs, is scattered throughout the collection.
  - 1972 Convention (Washington, D.C.)
    - T1-T3, 1 folder
      - International Information Systems Under Development [T-1A-C] (Box 173)
      - Modern Parliamentary Information Systems [T2] (Box 173)
      - Libraries and International Information Exchange [T3A-C] (Box 173)
    - T4-T6, 1 folder
      - International Uses of All U.S. Data Bases [T4A-B] (Box 173)
      - International Cooperation: Information Science Education and Research [T5A-B] (Box 173)
      - Shaping of International Information Systems by Technology [T6A-B] (Box 173)
    - T6-T8, 1 folder
      - Shaping of International Information Systems by Technology [T6C] (Box 173)
      - Social, Political and Economic Factors in International Information Flow [T7A-B] (Box 173)
      - Highlights [T8] (Box 173)
    - 1-7, 1 folder
      - SIG/Costs, Budgeting, and Economics (CBE) [1 and 1A] (Box 173)
      - Costing Information Activities: Information Supply [2A] (Box 173)
      - Costing Information Activities: Information Demand [2B] (Box 173)
      - SIG / Automated Language Processing (ALP) [3] (Box 173)
      - SIG/Technology, Information and Society (TIS) [4 A-B] (Box 173)
      - SIG/Foundations of Information Science (FIS) [5A-B] (Box 173)
      - Opening Session [6] (Box 173)
      - Copyright Debate [7 A-B] (Box 173)
    - 8-14, 1 folder